it is so good to be here and I've
noticed already how nice you people are
walking to the show tonight just a woman
ran up to me and she said I love your
hair
it's like you're going fast but you're
not
when I got here I looked in the mirror
and I'm like I'm going pretty fast
I mean look at the view it's almost like
I'm flying over you if you look at this
side it's ridiculous it's a little it's
crazy where is he going
oh I can see that look on your face
you're all wondering why Tony danz is in
your wonderful City tonight
some of the older people are like no
honey that's Henry Winkler he's here
times they're tough he's back on stage
again
the younger people are like man the
singer for the Chili Peppers is pretty
Haggard
[Applause]
well I see here tonight
oh my gosh you guys look great I know a
lot of you got that look on your face
like how Italian is this guy
are his eyebrows connecting yes by the
end of this set just one brow for you
I am Italian oh my gosh I'll tell you
this right now came from a big Italian
family you know and even as a little kid
I would run into the kitchen and I'd see
all the Italian women in there you know
my mom
you know my aunts grandma on there and I
just look at all these little Italian
women I was like they are so beautiful
and they are they are so beautiful and I
realize this little kid their Italian
women are so beautiful and as they get
older they they become handsome
[Applause]
your town your town and you're a woman
and I miss that
but your husband's gonna roll over and
see Tony Danza in bed about 10 years
you guys my mom was the first real man
in my life
I thought I had four grandpas to the
funeral I thought we were just
Progressive they're like no that's
grandma who's passed away Joey
I've been calling growling no no for the
last four years
oh yes Italian it's just different too
you know I was thinking today you know
even as a little kid growing up uh I
Dropped a Bomb on my family at 10 years
old because I came out as a magician
yeah I used to wear a cape with no shirt
on I had a wand trying to make people
disappear that weren't there
you know and to make it worse at 10
years old my dad got me my first bicycle
and it was a girl's bike
yeah you know a girl's bike and my dad
and I got into it I'm like Dad I don't
know if you know I'm a magician with a
lot of glitter on and a cape with no
shirt on it's been tough enough
but the girls bike's not helping my
situation dad and of course he's like
you're gonna let why do you think it's a
girl's bike what makes it a girl's bike
I'm like Dad it says country girl
written across the side
I can read dad
you're gonna let those words Define you
Joey uh yeah a little bit dad you let
those words Define what kind of man you
are uh yeah Dad I am I am because it's
not like it is today that if we saw this
shirtless boy you know riding in the
cape on the girl's bike you're just like
here's a trophy you win on your way
[Music]
go yes here's another trophy for you
just it wasn't like that then you know
and I'd get bullied I tell people all
the time I know what it's like to get
picked on because people would pick on
me you know I'd be riding my bike and
people would yell things and I told my
dad dad people are picking on me he's
like who I go mom
foreign
either grandma or grandpa I can't make
it out from here
but they're being aggressive
and I loved magic I loved my bike you
know at a certain point though I had to
give up magic it was tough
has anyone ever had to give up magic and
has anyone ever had give up something
that they love so much
no okay I should have moved here
for all your dreams come true
maybe I can move back and I can start
doing magic again
right
I had to give it up
I remember exactly where I was I was
alone I was like man am I ever gonna
meet a girl if I'm ever gonna have a
girlfriend in my life you know I gotta
put away the scarves
I gotta put away the Rings I gotta put a
shirt on and take the cape off
you know I had to get out I realized if
I was ever gonna have a woman in my life
I gotta quit
so at 36 I was out
country girl went for One Last Ride
what's up
thank you
it's so different
you've been walking around today I saw
McDonald's
I loved McDonald's when I was a kid
anyone else love McDonald's remember
remember if you're good let's get some
cholesterol come on let's go you know
McDonald's was a treat for me when my
kids were little McDonald's was a threat
I would threaten them I'm gonna take you
through the drive-thru no Dad don't do
it
saturated fats GMOs
guys I just found out gluten is not a
metal band from Germany I just found
that out
so I don't know what these other things
you're talking about are I loved
McDonald's as a kid
I remember my mom oh my gosh single
mother selling real estate you know
making it ends meet she would just wait
for me outside on a Friday in her car
and just yell Joey I'd come running out
get in the car honey we're going to
McDonald's oh my gosh get in the car she
put Elton John on it away we go to
McDonald's go in there and get whatever
you want can I mom yes can we eat in
this dirty parking lot yes we can
we're gonna sit in the car and eat
McDonald's that was enough
you know there was no video games there
was no iPhone just McDonald's in the car
I sit up front with her and she just
watched me shovel McDonald's into my fat
little Italian face
she'd roll the windows up so tight and
I'd shovel more McDonald's into my face
Bam Bam bams like Shark Week
while my mom smoked
yes smoking in the car a Virginia Slim
do you know what a Virginia slim is you
guys it's a cigarette it's it's a
cigarette it's like a flare it's it's a
cigarette this long you guys
just out of her mouth
she'd wave it around the car like it was
incense here you go honey
make sure everybody gets some
she'd roll the window down and tap on
the car next door what's going on in
there
foreign
not get scared Mom where are you ask for
my Big Mac so I know I'm alive
her little hand would come out here I am
honey
smoke everywhere
so much smoke I take a fry and I would
dip it in the smoke I would dip I'm
dipping the fries than the smoke just
pulling in toxins yes oh my gosh I love
you Mom I would sky right you're the
best mom I love you
dipping the fries in the smoke
out
you know why I'm dipping the fries in
the smoke
because no one had discovered ranch
dressing yet that's what I'm talking
about
imagine a world without ranch dressing
see how tight the room got right now
I don't like him talking about that
[Laughter]
the other night after a show I wanted to
go and a bunch of us were going to the
club next door and I didn't have my ID
and the young guy at the front door said
hey man I need to see some ID I need to
know you're old enough to get in here
I'm like bro look at this face
looks like a leather bag full of rocks
I don't care I need ID I had no ID and I
said check it out I'm
I'm and I pulled this
you know what that is this guy thinks
it's a vape
you remember using one of these it was a
while ago but you remember man
oh you got to tighten it up sometimes oh
that's the final haircut right
there sir you wear it well
oh my gosh would I lose in the shower I
wish I could give to you
[Applause]
not fair
if I could take an eyebrow off I'd throw
it on your head
I brought this into the into the into
the barn no one knew what it was people
were looking at me what's he gonna do
with that and I said it's just for the
eyebrows